<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Cities</string>

    <string name="city1">Chittagong</string>
    <string name="city2">Dhaka</string>
    <string name="city3">Coxbazar</string>
    <string name="city4">Sylhet</string>

    <string name="des_city1">Chittagong /tʃɪtəɡɒŋ/ (Bengali: চট্টগ্রাম Bengali pronunciation: [tʃɔt̠t̠ɔgram])
        is a major coastal seaport city and financial centre in southeastern Bangladesh.
    The city has a population of more than 2.5 million[1] while the metropolitan area has
        a population of 4,009,423 at the 2011 Census,making it the second largest city in the country.
        It is the capital of an eponymous district and division.
        The city is located on the banks of the Karnaphuli River between the Chittagong Hill Tracts and the Bay of Bengal.</string>
    <string name="des_city2">
Dhaka City across Buriganga River – a painting by Frederick William Alexander de Fabeck in 1861[1]

Dhaka, formerly spelled as Dacca in English, is the capital and one of the oldest cities of Bangladesh.
    The history of Dhaka begins with the existence of urbanised settlements in the area that is now Dhaka
        dating from the 7th century CE. The city area was ruled by the Buddhist kingdom of Kamarupa before
        passing to the control of the Sena dynasty in the 9th century CE.[2] After the Sena dynasty, Dhaka
        was successively ruled by the Turkic and Afghan governors descending from the Delhi Sultanate before
        the arrival of the Mughals in 1608. After Mughals, British ruled the region for over 150 years until
        the independence of India. </string>
    <string name="des_city3">
        Cox Bazar  is a city, fishing port,tourism centre and district headquarters in Bangladesh. The beach in Coxs Bazar is sandy and has a gentle
        slope; with a unbroken length of 155 km (96 mi), it is one of the longest sea beaches in the world.[2][3][4]
        It is located 150 km (93 mi) south of the industrial port of Chittagong. Cox's Bazar is also known by the name
        Panowa, which Translates literally as "yellow flower." Another old name was "Palongkee".

</string>
    <string name="des_city4">Sylhet (Bengali: সিলেট), Sylheti: ꠍꠤꠟꠐ), also known as Jalalabad, is a metropolitan
        city in northeastern Bangladesh. It is the administrative seat of Sylhet Division. The city is located on
        the right bank of the Surma River in northeastern Bengal. It has a subtropical climate and lush highland terrain.
        The city has a population of more than half a million.[1] Sylhet is one of Bangladesh's most important spiritual
        and cultural centres. It is one of the most important cities of Bangladesh, after Dhaka and Chittagong due to its
        importance to the country's economy. The city's dargahs, or burial sites of Muslim saints, attract several thousand
        devotees each year.</string>
</resources>
